<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CS342: Neural Networks on Greg Anderson</title>
    <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CS342: Neural Networks on Greg Anderson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homework 4</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework4/</guid>
      <description>In this homework, we will implement an object detector for the SuperTuxKart simulator. The goal is to look at an image and identify the locations of karts, bombs/projectiles, and pickup items. The dataset is the same as homework 3 and the starting code will look similar. You will need similar data augmentation to what you used in homework 3.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework 3</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework3/</guid>
      <description>For this homework, we will really tune our SuperTuxKart classifier in order to push the accuracy as high as possible. We will then extend that classifier to label each pixel of the input rather than each input image as a whole.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students. See details at the bottom of this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework 2</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework2/</guid>
      <description>For this homework, you will be classifying images from the SuperTuxKart dataset using a convolutional neural network.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students. See details at the bottom of this page.
Starter Code We provide some starter code for this homework here. This zip file contains the following:
 bundle.py, a script you can use to zip up your homework for submission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework 1</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework1/</guid>
      <description>In this first homework, you will be training a deep network to classify images from SuperTuxKart.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students. See details at the bottom of this page.
Running on Google Colab For this assignment, as well as future assignments, you may want access to a GPU to train your models more quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
