<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greg Anderson</title>
    <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Greg Anderson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gavlegoat.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homework 2</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework2/</guid>
      <description>For this homework, you will be classifying images from the SuperTuxKart dataset using a convolutional neural network.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students. See details at the bottom of this page.
Starter Code We provide some starter code for this homework here. This zip file contains the following:
 bundle.py, a script you can use to zip up your homework for submission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework 1</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/cs342/homework1/</guid>
      <description>In this first homework, you will be training a deep network to classify images from SuperTuxKart.
This assignment, as with all of the homework assignments, should be completed individually without sharing solutions, models, or ideas with other students. See details at the bottom of this page.
Running on Google Colab For this assignment, as well as future assignments, you may want access to a GPU to train your models more quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>My research broadly covers the intersection of programming languages and machine learning. In particular, I am most interested in developing techniques for proving the safety of systems with machine learning components. My early work in this domain has focused on using abstraction refinement to prove local robustness properties (PLDI&#39;19). More recently I have worked on incorporating ideas from PL research to develop a framework for deep reinforcement learning with formally guaranteed safety (NeurIPS&#39;20).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:06:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Neurosymbolic Reinforcement Learning with Formally Verified Exploration. Greg Anderson, Abhinav Verma, Isil Dillig, Swarat Chaudhuri. At NeurIPS &amp;lsquo;20. Tool available here.
Optimization and Abstraction: A Synergistic Approach for Analyzing Neural Network Robustness. Greg Anderson, Shankara Pailoor, Isil Dillig, and Swarat Chaudhuri. At PLDI&#39;19 (Distinguished Paper). Tool available here.
Learning Abstractions for Program Synthesis. Xinyu Wang, Greg Anderson, Isil Dillig, Ken McMillan. At CAV&#39;18.
Formal Analysis of the Compact Position Reporting Algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gavlegoat.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gavlegoat.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a 5thyear PhD student at UT Austin&amp;rsquo;s UToPiA and Trishul groups, advised by Isil Dillig and Swarat Chaudhuri. My research focuses on the intersection of program analysis and machine learning. Specifically, I&amp;rsquo;m interested in developing tools and techniques which can analyze machine learning systems to guarantee safety. Before joining the UToPiA group I received my BS in Computer Engineering and Mathematics from the University of Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
